Finding Aid for the Grantland Rice Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Photographs
  - Index to Identified Photographs
    - Cooper, Robin (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Cooper, Will (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Corbitt, Elmore
    - Coulon, Johnny (Box 12, Folder 20, Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Cox, James H. (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Craven, Frank (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Crosby, Bing (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Crowley, Jim (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Curry, George (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Cyma Distinguished Service Award (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Daley, George (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Daniels, --- (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Dark, Alvin (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Dawson, Red (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Demaret, Jimmy (dinner) (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Dempsey, Jack (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Dempsey, Jack - training camp (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Digby, Mr. and Mrs. Fred (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Dixie, Marilyn (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Dunn, Joseph "Red" (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Durrell, Oliver H. (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Dyer, Braven (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - East, Victor (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Edwards, Ralph, Christine, and children (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Erroll, Leon (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Field, Bill, Frances, and children (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Field, Bryan (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Field, Kenny, Jessica, and Billy (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Flamingo Hotel (Miami) (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Fleming, Major P.B. (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Fleming, Neil (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Football (school team with G. Kice) (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Forbes, B.C. (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Forbes, Harry (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Fowler, Gene (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Fowler, Willie and Mike (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Furillo, Bud (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Gallico, Paul (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Gardner, George (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Garrett, Paul (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Gee, Smith (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Glesson, Edgar "Scoop" (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Gordon, Edwynne Pillow (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Graham, Frank (Box 2, Folder 7, 9)
    - Great Falls, Montana (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Harron, Bob (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Havanna, Cuba (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Havoc, June (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Hazelden Farm (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Hazelden Farm - Golf Course (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Helms Hall Board (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Helms, Paul H., Jr. (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Henderson, Dan (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Herd, Fred and Jim (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Hickman, Herman (Box 12, Folder 7, 9)
    - Holline, Eddie (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Hot Springs, Va. (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Howard, Mr. and Mrs. Charles (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Howell, Bob (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Husing, Ted (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Hutchinson, Jock (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Ichauway Plantation (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Igoe, Herman "Hype" (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Irwin, May (house and island) (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Jackson, Edwin (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Jackson, Watt (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - James, Dennis (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Johnson, Allen (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Jones, Bobby (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Jones, H.A. "Jimmy" (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Jones, ' W.A. (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Kahn, Alex (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Kelland, Clarence Budington (Box 11, Folder 26, 28, Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Kelly, Bob (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Key Largo, Fla. (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Kibbee, Guy (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Kirkwood, Joe (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Knox, Jim (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Kyle, Mr. and Mrs. E.J. (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - La Cava, Gregory (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Lakeside Course (L.A.) (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Lardner, Hing (Box 11, Folder 24, Box 12, Folder 1, 4, 13, 22)
    - Law, John (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Levine, Alf (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Little, Lou (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Loftus, Charlie (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Look Magazine All-America (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Lord, Lieut R.B. (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Los Angeles Open (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Machamer, J--- (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Marston, Max (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Maxwell, Lee (Box 11, Folder 28, 31)
    - Maxwell, Ray (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - McAdam, C--- (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - McColloms (Adirondacks) (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - McLwan, John (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - McKeener, Ed (dinner) (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - McLaughrey, Tuss (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - McSamara, Tommy (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - "Mexican Hayride" cast (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Miami Beach (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Milburn, Devereux (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Miller, Don (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Mohr, Jack (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Montague, John (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Montauk Downs, L.I. (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Moore, Hugh (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Mullin, Willard (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Myers, Robert (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - National Broadcasting Co. (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - National Links (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - National Open Golf Tournament (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Neale, Earle Greasy (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Nelson, Battling (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Newman, Harry (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Newman, Dr. L.A. (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Oheru, Jack and Jim (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Osgood River (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Osterweis, Kathryn (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Palm Beach Country Club (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Palmer, Bud (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Patterson, Paul (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Perry, Lawrence (Box 1, Folder 32, Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Pilcher, C--- (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Pitts, Jack (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Pratt, Lowell (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Preston, James and May (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Priggs, Eddie III (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Raleigh cigarette advertisement (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Raleigh, N.C. (V/PTF) (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Red Cross War Drive (Box 2, Folder 1, 7)
    - Reddick, Ford (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Reilly, Fir. and Mrs. F.D. "Hap" (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Reveille (book) (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Reynolds, Quentin (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Rheingold advertisements (Box 11, Folder 13, 21, 37)
    - Rice, Dale Snowden (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Rice, Florence (Box 1, Folder 27, Box 2, Folder 1, 26, 57)
    - Rice, Grantland III (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Richards, Vinnie (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Ridley, Brom (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Roosevelt, Quentin (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Roosevelt, Theodore (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Roy, Malcolm (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Russell, Fred (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Ryan, Buddy (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Ryan, Fritz and Elizabeth, house (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Sarnuelson, Rube (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Santa Anita (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Santoro, Al (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Sasse, Major R.I. (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Schroeder, Bill (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Sharp, Frank (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Sherrill, Sidney (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Shor, Toots (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Shute, Denny (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Sims, P. Hal (Box 1, Folder 28, Box 2, Folder 13, 14)
    - Siwanoy Snowbirds (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Slocum, Bill (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Smith, Red (Box 2, Folder 7, 9)
    - Snavely, Carl (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Snowbirds, Siwanoy (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Spartan Valor (horse) (Box 2, Folder 7, 20)
    - Speaker, Tris (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Sports Writers Dinner (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Stankys, The (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Stein, William (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Stephens, Joe (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Steppin Pappy (horse) (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Stiles, Maxwell (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Stuhldreher, Harry (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Sunshine Park (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Sweetser, Jess (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Tabler, Percy (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Taylor, Mrs. Sec (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Teagle, Walter (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Thomas, Frank (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Thorpe, Jim (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Tilden, Bill (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Trevor, George (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Trippi, Charley (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Trumbull, Walter (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Tunney, Gene (Box 11, Folder 26, 27, Box 12, Folder 9)
    - "21" Brands Inc. (dinner) (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Twombly, Henry (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Ulrich, Frank (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Van Surdam, H.R. (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Vanderbilt baseball (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Village Green Reading Society (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - WABD Radio (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Wallace, Frank (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Wee Loch, Easthampton (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Wells, Capt. W.H. (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - West Palm Beach Country Club (Box 11, Folder 4, 5)
    - West, Ricard (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Wheeler, John (Box 11, Folder 24, 26)
    - Whipple, Col. S. (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - White, Gilbert (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - White, Walter (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Williamson, Logan (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Wilson, Arlo (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - WNOE radio (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Woodruff, Robert W. (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Ichauway Plantation (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Worrall, C.B. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - WPTF football banquet (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Wright, Charlie G. (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Yawkey, Mabel(?) (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Young, Lou (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Ziff, Sid (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Zimmerman, Paul (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Zuppke, Bob (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Photographs of Grantland Rice Alone (Box 11, Folder 1-22)
    - World War I and early snapshots (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous snapshots (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Hunting (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Golfing (Box 11, Folder 4-8)
    - Hatless (Box 11, Folder 9-14)
    - Wearing a Hat (Box 11, Folder 15-22)
  - Photographs of Grantland Rice with other persons
    - World War I and early snapshots (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Golfing (Box 11, Folder 24-28)
    - Hunting, Fishing, etc. (Box 11, Folder 29-31)
    - Dinners (Box 11, Folder 32-38)
    - Movie and Play Casts (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 2-8)
  - Photographs of Grantland Rice memorials (Box 12, Folder 9-11)
    - V.U. bust, plaque, Sunshine Park race, dinner, memorial award (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Murfreesboro birthplace plaque (Box 12, Folder 10-11)
  - Photographs of other persons (Box 12, Folder 12-27)
    - World War I and early snapshots (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Golfing (Box 12, Folder 13-15)
    - Hunting, Fishing, etc. (Box 12, Folder 16-17)
    - Babies and Children (Box 12, Folder 18-19)
    - Sporting (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Nonsporting (Box 12, Folder 21-25)
    - Florence Rice (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Winston Churchill (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Photographs of scenes (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Photographic negatives (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Drawings of Grantland Rice etc. (Box 12, Folder 30-31)
  - Picture book on Ichauway Plantation, with pictures of GB etc. (Box 12, Folder 30-31)
  - Photographs of sports figures, alphabetically arranged, used in connection with Sports Parade column (Box 13, Box 14)
- Personal, Business, and Public Affairs of Grantland Rice
  - Certificates (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Certificates awarded to GR (6 items): U.S. Army Hon. Discharge (1919), Suffolk County Sheriff's Office (1929), U.S. Treasury Dept. (194), War Finance Committee of New York (1944), American Theatre Wing War Service (n.d.), Tennessee Sports Hall of Fame (1966)
  - Programs, invitations, etc. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Programs, invitations, etc., 1912-52 (2). Capital City Club (1912), Alumni Coaches Association (1926), Jack Dempsey Dinner (1936), Knickerbocker Country Club (n.d.), Metropolitan Club Grand National Sweepstake Dinner (1947} Arthur Baer Dinner (1949), Empire City Racing Association (1950), Grantland Rice Dinner (1951), Sunshine Park (1952), Maryland Jockey Club (1950).
  - Contracts, 1911, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Contracts, 1911, 1925. (3) Mail and Express Company and Grantland Rice, Dec. 30, 1911; New York Tribune Inc. and Grantland Rice, July 2, 1925.
  - Film Company Papers (Box 15, Folder 4-10)
    Sportlight Company papers (4-8); "Follow the Sun" cast and schedule (8); Spalding Brothers film prospectus (ms. by Lou Little; 22 typed pages).
  - Stock Certificates (Box 15, Folder 11-13)
    Stock certificates (11-13). Golf Publishing Company (3), American Woman's Realty Corporation (l), Blind Brook Realty Co. (2), World Bestos Corporation (6), Arcturus Radio Tube Company (l), Grantland Rice Sport-lights (2), Sirian Lamp Company (2), Augusta National Golf Club (1), Grantland Rice Sport Pictures Corp. (l), The National Golf Review (6).
  - Apartment lease, 1158 Fifth Avenue, N.Y., Oct. 23, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Bills, notices etc; booklet listing members (including GR) of The Coffee House club (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Membership cards, press passes etc. (Box 15, Folder 15)
    Membership cards, press passes etc. (15) Base Ball Writers' Association, Football Writers Association, Los Angeles Press Club, country and golf clubs etc.
  - Miscellaneous papers: stock, taxes, insurance, V.U. Alumni records, Bundles for Britain sweater directions etc. (Box 15, Folder 16-18)
  - Appraised Valuation of the Furnishings of the Residence of Grantland Rice... East Hampton, L.I., Sept. 30, 1930. (66 typed pages, bound) (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Funeral register, Grantland Rice's funeral (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Estate papers (Box 15, Folder 21-22)
  - NANA Board of Directors, Resolution (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Items removed from books belonging to Grantland Rice, now in Special Collections (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Souvenirs: awards, buttons, medals, etc. (Box 16)
    Writers associations membership buttons: Lawn Tennis Writers Association, 11 buttons, for 1936, 1937, 1939, 1940, 1941, 1942, 1945, 1946, 1948, 1949, 1950; Football Writers Association, 4 buttons, for 1936, 1937, N.Y., etc.; Baseball Writers Association of America, 1 button, n.d.; N.Y. Turf Writers Association, 1 button, n.d.; Golf Writers Association of America, 1 button, n.d.
    World Series buttons: 1927 (Pittsburgh), 1933 (Washington, D.C.), 1936 (Yankee Stadium), 1938 (Chicago), 194l (Brooklyn Dodgers), 1942 (Yankees), 1943 (Yankees), 1945 (Chicago Cubs), 1946 (St. Louis), 1947 (2 buttons: Yankees and Dodgers), 1948 (Braves), 1949 (St. Louis), 1950 (Yankees). Total: 14 buttons.
    Horse racing press buttons (10 buttons): Santa Anita Park (4 octagonal, 1 round; 3 numbered 41, 1 each 66 and 83); Sunshine Park, 1950; Belmont Park (2), 1950, 1953; Garden State Park, 1950; Monmouth Park, 1947.
    Golf medals, badges etc (11 items): Augusta National Golf Club, Masters Tournament (4 items), 1 engraved medal, "Grantland Rice/ Masters Tournament / 1949", 1 round badge with ribbon, 1935, 2 rectangular badges with ribbons, "Augusta Nat'l Golf Club" and "Masters Tournament 1942"; Bing Crosby (2 medals), "Contestant... 1940" and "Championship... 1942"; United States Golf Association Press (2 medals), n.d.; Colonial Club Open Tournament, 194l (1 medal); Pomonok Country Club, 1939 P.G.A. Championship (1 badge); 1 gold medal "1928 Collier's / The National Weekly / Jingle Tournament / Luck Piece" engraved "G.R."
    Olympics press badges and medal (4 items): 8th Olympiad, Paris, 1924; 10th Olympiad, Los Angeles, 1932; 11th Olympiad, Berlin, 1936; large medal in red box, XI Olympiad, Berlin, 1936.
    Vanderbilt University items (5 buttons): 1 large black and gold VU button with yellow ribbon; 3 football-shaped Touchdown Club buttons; 1 small VU Quinq button.
    3 name-tags with footballs on ribbons.
    Hotels, restaurants etc.: key from The Belvedere, Baltimore; horseshoe from French Lick Springs Hotel, The Home of Pluto, The Kentucky Derby; U.S. cent with metal border, "Dinner at the Stork Club"; medal from "Jack and Charlie's 21 West Fifty-Second Street"; metal plate, "The Lexington extends the courtesies of The Silver Grill to Grantland Rice" etc.
    Miscellaneous medals, buttons etc.: New York, National Convention Committee, Democratic National Convention, 1924 (with Tennessee Subcommittee ribbon); Special Investigator, Minneapolis, Minn.; London, Tenth Hackney; for loyal help in building the Stadium, Ross-Ade Field, Purdue University, 1924; GR / This Is Your Life; Humanity and Public Service above Personal Gratification, 1907-1928, RMC; Sportsmanship Brotherhood; fleur-de-lis with eagle; State of Hawaii, 1959, The Aloha State, August 21, 1959 etc; 3 Navy Relief Society buttons, with red anchor etc.; 1 Fight Cancer button; The Salvation/Women's Voluntary Services button.
    Miscellaneous other items: 1 sterling silver card case: "HGR Sept. 28-07" with sea nymphs; 1 ashtray "Staple Sam the Markwell man"; 1 metal plate "1928 Del Monte Forest Property owner Del Monte Properties Co. Del Monte Calif."; 1 rubber home plate, "SR Major League Sav-a-Leg Home Plate / Patented/ Official/ The Seamless Rubber Co. New Haven, Conn. 1 pipe tool; 1 skate key; 1 package Loewe Buttons; 1 package Ronson flints; 1 button "EKC"; 1 leather package resin (?)$ 1 wishbone; 1 key (to inlaid wooden box - see below).
    World War J souvenirs: 1 blue felt patch with white A and red circle; 3 button-on felt insigniae: red with gold pineapple (?) and number 88, grey with red crown and R III, grey with red number 36; 1 metal belt buckle, with crown and "Gott mit uns; 1 7-pointed leaf-shaped badge; 1 German I.D. tag; 1 piece of rubber; 1 small wooden box, label "Valeur en toutes lettres, envoi" etc.; 1 leather pouch (in which were contained World War I orders, passes etc., now in box 2, folders 34-37).
    1 folder of notes, notebooks, business cards etc.; 1 roll recording tape; 1 memorandum book.
- Writings neither by nor about Grantland Rice
  - Poems, typescript and separately printed, by other people (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Clippings of poems by other people (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Mimeograph copy of Gene Fowler's "The Jervis Bay Goes Down" (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Galley proof of Betsey Barton's And Now to Live Again (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Galley proof of John McNulty's "The Slugger Comes into His Own" (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Manuscripts probably by other people (unsigned) (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Press release, Winston Churchill, "The Story of My Early Life" (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Printed songs and sheet music not by Grantland Rice (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - "Album of Poetical Extracts" by other people, apparently kept by Grantland Rice (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Book, by Hek, verse by Hugh Keough (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Last issue of N.Y. Sun, Jan. 44, 1930; first issue of World Telegram-Sun, Jan. 5, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous issues of The Stars and Stripes, Aug. 23, 1918-May 30, 1919 (Box 18, Folder 2-15)
  - Newspaper clippings neither by nor about Grantland Rice
    - About friends and associates (Box 18, Folder 16-18)
      Clippings about friends and associates: Bruce Barton, Albert A. Boyden, Irvin S. Cobb, Frank Condon, Frank Crowninshield, Gene Fowler, Rube Goldberg, Percy Hammond, Steve Hannagan, Clarence Budington Kelland (16), Ring Lardner (17), Henry McLemore, John McNulty, John Patterson, Westbrook Pegler, Harold Ross, Toots Shor, Gene Symonds, John Wheeler, Robert Woodruff etc. (18).
    - About baseball (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - About football (Box 19, Folder 1-3)
    - About golf (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - About miscellaneous sports (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - About Georgia (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - About politics and public affairs (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous clippings (Box 19, Folder 8-9)
  - Miscellaneous Booklets, Pamphlets, and Other Publications (Box 19, Folder 10-16)
    "Maxims of Napoleon," "Nothing Could Conquer Him (F.D. Roosevelt)," "Mr. (Dan) McGugin Alone," "Greville Gumming 1922-194," "The Story of My Early Life" (Churchill prospectus), Ross Allen's Reptile Institute series, Jack Knox prints, "Neither Free Nor Equal" (WCC0 radio script series), The Phi Beta Kappa Key (Oct. 1931), True Temper Garden Book, Instructions for Operating and Maintaining the Portable Typewriter Hermes Baby, Instructions for Edison Light-o-matic Radio Receivers, Typical Editorials from The New York Tribune, The Adult Quarterly (July-Sept. 1933), The U.S. Steel Quarterly (Nov. 1930), "Crisis" (Vanderbilt Univ. publication), 2 brochures on will-making.
- Sports Guides, Booklets, and Other Publications
  - Baseball booklets (Box 20, Folder 1)
    "Chicago Cardinals 1948 Press, Radio and Television Guide," "Who's Who in the American League"
  - Baseball miscellaneous material (Box 20, Folder 2-3)
  - Boxing miscellaneous material; Basketball (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Football Booklets (Box 20, Folder 5-6)
    "Southeastern Conference Press and Radio Dope Book," "Official Football Review, University of Notre Dame, 1930," "Official Football Rules 1919," "The Football Fan's Dope Book," "Football for the Fan."
  - Football miscellaneous material (Box 20, Folder 7-8)
  - Golf Booklets, "Rules of Golf 1934," "Records of the Masters Tournament," "Rights and Wrongs of Golf," "Expert Advice on Playing Golf," The Metropolitan Golfer (Sept. 1923) (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Golf miscellaneous material (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Horce racing booklets (Box 20, Folder 11-14)
    The American Bloodstock Review (Nov. 29, 194l), The November Stake Bulletin (1948), "New York Racing Press Information 1948," "The Golden Jubilee Preakness Stakes," "Ten Years of Racing in New Jersey," "American Champions and Two Year Olds 1951," "Review of the Year, Westchester Racing Association, 1948."
  - Horse racing miscellaneous material (Box 20, Folder 15-16)
  - Olympic Games miscellanous material (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Spalding's Baseball Guide, 1906, 1907, 1908, 1909, 1910, 1911, 1912, 1913, 1914, 1917, 1920, 1921, 1923, 1924, 1925, 1927, 1936 (Box 21)
  - Spalding's Baseball Guide, 1906, 1907, 1908, 1909, 1910, 1911, 1912, 1913, 1914, 1917, 1920, 1921, 1923, 1924, 1925, 1927, 1936 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous baseball guides, 1872; 1906; 1911-1913; 1943-1945 (Box 22, Folder 2-4)
    Miscellaneous baseball guides: 1872 (reprint of first guide), 1906 (Lajoie), 1911 (Constitution and Rules), 1913 (Reach), 1943 (Commissioner), 1945 (Barnes), How to Umpire (Spalding)
  - Spalding's Baseball Record (Box 22, Folder 5)
    Spalding's Baseball Record, 1912, 1913, 1914, 1915, 1917, 1920, 1921, 1922, 1923, 1924
  - Spalding's Baseball Record (Box 23, Folder 1-4)
  - Sporting News Record Book and Guide, 1923-1924; 1941-1948 (Box 23, Folder 5-6)
    Sporting News Record Book and Guide, 1923, 1924, 194l, 1942, 1943, 1945, 1948
  - Who's Who in Baseball (Box 23, Folder 7)
    Who's Who in Baseball, 1916, 1918, 1922, 1923, 1924, 1925, 1926, 1927, 1928, 1929, 1932, 1936, 1940, 1941, 1942, 1943, 1949, 1951, 1952, 1953
  - Who's Who in Baseball (Box 24, Folder 1-2)
  - The Baseball Bat Bag; Famous Slugger Yearbook (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - The Little Red Book of Major League Baseball, 1934, 1940-42, 1943-46, 1949-52, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 3-8)
  - Spalding's Football Rules (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Spalding's Football Guide, 1903-1910, 1913-1915, 1917, 1921-1925, 1927, 1929-1933, 1935, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 1-9)
  - Spalding's Football Guide, 1903-1910, 1913-1915, 1917, 1921-1925, 1927, 1929-1933, 1935, 1940 (Box 26, Folder 1-4)
  - Miscellaneous football guides (Box 26, Folder 5-7)
    Miscellaneous football guides - 1941, 1942, 194- (Barnes); 1949 (Spink); 1950 (NCAA); "How to Play Football" (Spalding, 1927)
  - Spalding's Golf Guide, 1906, 1913 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Spalding's Golf Guide, 1916, 1918 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Spalding's Boxing Rules (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Everlast Boxing Record (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Spalding's Lawn Tennis Annual, 1912, 1916, 1917 (Box 27, Folder 2-3)
  - Spalding's Polo Guide (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Athletic Almanac (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Intercollegiate Wrestling Guide (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - All-Sports Record Book (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Reach Basketball Guide (Box 27, Folder 5)